

in LinkedIn

GITHUB

## Suf Karmon

I believe the best results are achieved through multi – disciplinary collaboration. So I have dedicated the past 9 years doing so. Now looking to contribute as a software developer. Combination of a software developer's knowledge, experience of a technological units alumni, and elite military fighter's mentality – all in one.

### **Programing skills**

Frontend: HTML, CSS, Java-script

Backend: PHP

- MySQL, JSON
- C, C++

### Work experience

2019-2022

# IDF - Product manager / C4I department (Command Control Communications and Intelligence)

Lead the development of 3 'In house' command & control systems Initiated an 'operative need' from prototype development to full operational use and expanding to every small vessel in the Navy

2.5 years experience in Agile software development methods

Initiated digital transformation of navy commando vessels to integrate independent systems under a local cloud and shared resources.

Responsible for the full product life-cycle from early requirements, architecture, budget, roadmap, integration, development and prioritization alongside the R&D team

2017-2019

#### Captain / Commander of a navy patrol boat

In charge of a crew of 14 soliders and the Captain of the ship Responsible for combat missions, training programs, technical maintenance, and general well – being of the soldiers

2013-2016

**Cadet / Naval Academy Course ("Hovlim")** 

#### **Education**

2020 - PRESENT

#### **B.Sc Software Engineering / Shenkar**

Current GPA 87

Major	<ul><li>Web</li></ul>	and	cloud	development.	Integrating	UI/UX	system	designs
Main o	courses	:						

2020

## **Product manager course / IDF** school of Computer and Cyber **Professions ("Basmach")**

2014-2015

#### **B.A Political Science / Haifa University**

Final GPA: 90

2009-2011

#### **Mevoot Iron high school**

Major – computer science, English translation, and music

#### **Volunteering**

Instructor of mentally challenged children in an educational program using sailing Community service "Shnat sheirut" - instructor of youth groups in the 'AUY' leading groups of teenagers in leadership and social activism work

Languages:

Hebrew – native, English - native